

# KEY SKILLS

- Web technologies:
  - OutSystems.

#### Front-end:

- HTML5.
- CSS3 & SASS.
- Bootstrap.
- Google Material Design.
- JavaScript.
- jQuery.
- React.js
- Vue.js

## Back-end:

- PHP.
- Laravel.
- Node.is
- REST APIs.
- Mobile development:
  - -React Native.
  - -OutSystems Mobile.
- Database and ORM:
  - SQL.
  - NoSQL.
- Versioning and Control:
  - Git.
  - GitHub/BitBucket.
- Tools:
  - Adobe Photoshop.
  - Adobe Xd.

## Yaser M. Saleh

## Software Engineer

Mobile: +962790809202

Email: YaserMuhammedJaser@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/yasersaleh/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/yasersaleh/</a>

Portfolio: https://yasermj.github.io/yaser/

## **OBJECTIVE**

An ambitious Software Engineer specialized in web development with a sense of simplicity and creativity that has effectively prototype and developed responsive user pleasuring products. A regular volunteer and a participant in IT events and meetups.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Software Developer – Nesma

Mar 2020 – Present

Certified web and mobile OutSystems developer that is actively developing, planning and maintaining enterprise and automated highend, simplicity-based and creative solutions.

• GIS Developer – InfoGraph

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

Esri ArcGIS based mapping and infographic web solutions implementation and integration.

## **EDUCATION**

• Coding Academy by Orange

June 2019 - Dec 2019

One of the top trainees with high evaluation scores and 10+ practical projects. Actively leading, planning and coming up with agile creative ideas.

• B.Sc. degree – Computer Science:

2015 - 2019

- Al Hussein bin Talal University.
- Ranked #1 on CS 2015 and #3 on the IT college -2019.
- GPA &Rating: 79 Very good.

• General Secondary certificate – IT Stream:

2012 - 2013

- Rosary Sisters School.
- GPA: 77.